<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Event on </title>
    <link>https://cybersec.upvision.co/categories/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Event on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cybersec.upvision.co/categories/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberSecNITD meetup with IEEE NITD student branch</title>
      <link>https://cybersec.upvision.co/events/feb19ieeemeetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersec.upvision.co/events/feb19ieeemeetup/</guid>
      <description>Today we collaborated with IEEE NITD Student Branch and organized a Introductory workshop.
Since being an independent club with students of common interest we thought it would be better if we do some serious workshop helping the freshman year students jump into the CyberSecurity Band Wagon!
The crowd we received was impressive! We never had a meetup with such a huge crowd before.
Since we are bunch of students with mediocre GPA trying to bust our keyboard typing out cryptic words what we describe as commands on dumb boring terminal doesn&amp;rsquo;t easily qualify as a Club with organization and publicity, today was important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root CTF 2018</title>
      <link>https://cybersec.upvision.co/events/rootctf18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersec.upvision.co/events/rootctf18/</guid>
      <description>The time has come to do it again!
Root CTF, a CTF event organized by CyberSecNITD every year in TerraTechnica NITD&amp;rsquo;s Annual Techfest.
The CTF was Jeopardy style and was conducted in offline mode.
We witnessed 11 teams having students from NITD and from other Colleges too. That was a huge progress for us from RootCTF17 where all our participants were students from NITD only.
Since last year&amp;rsquo;s CTF, we got the opportunity to learn more on topics in CyberSecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>